Frank J. Becker Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
Frank J. Becker Papers 1953-1964, 1974
nam_apap224
22.44 cubic ft.
Becker, Frank John, 1899-1981
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, University at Albany, SUNY
The Frank J. Becker Papers document Becker's service in the U.S Congress, as a representative of Nassau County (N.Y.), where he served from 1953-1964. The collection includes correspondence, subject files, and legislation from his tenure.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of select files in Series 1 and 2. Researchers seeking access to this material should contact the head of archives.
Red asterisks (***) denote restricted items.
Acquisition Information
Frank Becker initially donated his papers to Syracuse University in 1964. The oral history interview was posthumously donated in 1982 by Former Members of Congress, Inc. In 2006, all the papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical Sketch
Frank J. Becker was born in Brooklyn, New York on August 27, 1899 and moved with his family to Lynbrook, Long Island in 1905. He attended Brown’s Business College in Jamaica, Long Island. Becker enlisted in the United States Army on July 22, 1918 and during World War I served overseas in both England and France. In the 1930s, Becker founded a real-estate and insurance company, and was chairman emeritus of the Board of Directors of the Suburbia Federal Savings and Loan Association in Garden City, Long Island. Becker was an active member in both chapters of Veterans of Foreign Wars and American Legion in Lynbrook in addition to being a member of the Knights of Columbus.
From 1945-1953, Becker served as a member of the New York State Assembly representing Nassau County, Long Island. Beginning in 1952, Becker acted as the delegate to the Republican National Convention and in November 1952, Becker was elected as a Republican to Congress as a New York State Representative for the 3rd District, serving portions of Nassau County. In Becker’s final term from 1962-1964, congressional district lines were redrawn throughout Nassau County resulting in Becker acting as Representative of the 5th District.
During his terms in office, Becker was part of numerous committees and subcommittees including: Ways and Means Committee, Armed Services Committee (including the Subcommittee of Research and Development), Joint Legislative Committee for the Study of Military Law (specifically 1948-1953), and Charitable and Religions Societies Committee. Towards his later years in office, Becker became vocal and the focus of a debate regarding religion in schools. Becker sponsored a Constitutional amendment to allow Bible readings and organized prayer in public schools with voluntary participation. Following a Supreme Court Decision ruling prayer in school to be unconstitutional, the amendment was defeated.
Becker passed away on September 4, 1981 and is interned at Pine Law National Cemetery, Pinelawn, N.Y. Becker was survived by his wife of 58 years and his three children. One of his children, Francis X Becker was Mayor of Lynbrook and later served as a New York State Supreme Court Justice on Long Island.
The majority of the Frank J. Becker Papers span the years of 1953-1964 and document Becker’s tenure in the U.S. Congress representing a portion of Nassau County, New York. There also is a 1974 oral history interview with Becker recorded by Former Members of Congress, Inc. as part of its project "The Modern Congress in American History." The collection contains materials related to his day-to-day activities including correspondence, legislative files, subject specific files, printed matter, and items related to committee work. The collection does not contain personal correspondence or information regarding Becker’s time in the New York State Assembly.
The series arrangement reflects the way that Becker and his Congressional staff organized and filed his papers. The archivist also elected to retain the folder titles created by Becker and his staff. As original order is preserved, there is noticeable overlap of materials between series. Although Series 2 is entitled “Correspondence”, correspondence between Becker and constituents and other representatives and department heads is found throughout the entire collection. In addition, Series 4 is entitled “Congressional Record,” but there are clippings from the Congressional Record in other series.
Please note that in Series 1: Subject Files, materials of personal nature regarding some of Becker’s constituents is found in a number of folders and these records are restricted.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Subject Files, 1953-1964, 1974
Series 2 - Correspondence, 1953-1964
Series 3 - Legislative Files, 1953-1964, Undated
Series 4 - Congressional Record and Related Materials, 1958-1964
Series 1 and 2 are arranged alphabetically by subject. Series 3 is arranged chronologically by legislation introduction date. Series 4 is arranged chronologically as well.
Subject and Genre Headings
Politics and Politicians; Becker, Frank John, 1899-1981.; United States. Congress. House.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Armed Services.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Armed Services. Research and Development Subcommittee.; United States. Congress. House. Committee on Ways and Means.; Civil Rights--legislation and jurisprudence--United States.; Immigrants--New York (State)--Correspondence.; Prayer in the public schools--Law and legislation--United States.; Veterans--United States--New York (State).; New York (State)--Politics and government; Bills (legislative records); Clippings; Congressional Records; Correspondence; Files by subject; Legislative records
Container List
- Subject Files, 1953-1964; 1974; nam_apap224-1; 15.04 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains the general subject files of Representative Becker’s office including: letters, memos, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, reports, various Congressional Record clippings, informational booklets, photographs, original legislation, petitions, speeches, statements, and constituent correspondence. The 1974 oral history is included in this series. Select folders also contain an array of documents that contains individual constituent information of a sensitive nature. Researchers seeking access to these materials should contact the head of archives.
  The items in folders marked “Academies Lists-Annapolis, West Point, Air Force, Kings Point” 1953-1964 were originally housed in binders. For preservation purposes, the archivist unbound and foldered the items, but kept the materials in their original order.
  - Academy Appointments, Allstadt, Louis, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Academy Appointments, Andrews, Richard E., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1958-1959; nam_apap224-1_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academy Appointments, Barth, Ralph C., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1961; nam_apap224-1_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academy Appointments, Bjelland, Ronald, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academy Appointments, Colletti, Alan, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academy Appointments, Cullen, James M., West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1958-1962; nam_apap224-1_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academy Appointments, Eggers, John Jr., Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academy Appointments, Ermak, Donald, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academy Appointments, Fagan, Jeffrey, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academy Appointments, Fitzpatrick, William Jr., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1961; nam_apap224-1_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academy Appointments, Fowler, Joseph, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academy Appointments, Geller, Kenneth, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Academy Appointments, Gnecco, James, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1962; nam_apap224-1_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Academy Appointments, Gunderson, Jon, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Academy Appointments, Howley, Robert, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Academy Appointments, Hubbard, Richard, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Academy Appointments, Hubert, George, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Academy Appointments, Kantz, Philip, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963; nam_apap224-1_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Academy Appointments, Kollender, David, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Academy Appointments, Leitner, Frederick K., Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Academy Appointments, McCullough, Theodore V. Jr, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Academy Appointments, Neitz, Michael, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Academy Appointments, Nussbaum, Robert, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Academy Appointments, Palmer, Edwin A., Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1962; 1964; nam_apap224-1_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Academy Appointments, Rademacher, John, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1962; nam_apap224-1_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Academy Appointments, Rowan, Robert, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Academy Appointments, Staley, Edmund, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1962; nam_apap224-1_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Academy Appointments, Reichert, William, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1962-1964; nam_apap224-1_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Academy Appointments, Trotta, Peter, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Academy Appointments, Tschinart, John, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Academy Appointments, Weiler, William G., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1964; nam_apap224-1_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Academy Appointments, Weissner, William, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Academy Appointments, Wilkinson, John, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1960-1961; nam_apap224-1_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Academy Appointments, Zino, Richard, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964; nam_apap224-1_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Academy Graduates, Berkowitz, Michael C., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Academy Graduates, Bobko, Karol, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1959; nam_apap224-1_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Academy Graduates, Bobko, Peter B., Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962; nam_apap224-1_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Academy Graduates, Brindley, Peter, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1951; 1953-1958; 1960; nam_apap224-1_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Academy Graduates, Bunting, Keith, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1953-1955; 1957-1958; nam_apap224-1_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Academy Graduates, Clement, Donald, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962; nam_apap224-1_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Academy Graduates, Coles, Ronald R., Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Academy Graduates, Colletti, John, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1963; nam_apap224-1_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Academy Graduates, Connolly, Robert, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962; nam_apap224-1_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Academy Graduates, Crowley, Francis III, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1952-1958; nam_apap224-1_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Academy Graduates, Dina, Michael, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1959; 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Academy Graduates, Fieldman, Henry, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; 1960-1962; nam_apap224-1_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Academy Graduates, Fitch, Robert, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1957; 1961; nam_apap224-1_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Academy Graduates, Fitzpatrick, Walter, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1961; 1964; nam_apap224-1_48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Academy Graduates, Flanagan, William F., Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1963; nam_apap224-1_49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Academy Graduates, Ganley, John, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962; nam_apap224-1_50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Academy Graduates, Garfield, Peter, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1960; nam_apap224-1_51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Academy Graduates, Haemer, Eric John, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Academy Graduates, Heine, Joel, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1963; nam_apap224-1_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Academy Graduates, Henshaw, Robert, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1962; nam_apap224-1_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Academy Graduates, Herold, Lance, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1952-1955; 1957-1958; 1960; nam_apap224-1_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Academy Graduates, Hollerman, Richard, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1957; 1960; nam_apap224-1_56 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Academy Graduates, Hufschmid, Robert, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_57 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Academy Graduates, Josefson, Raymond, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1960; nam_apap224-1_58 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Academy Graduates, Keenan, William V Jr, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1963; nam_apap224-1_59 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Academy Graduates, Knoblock, Richard, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1961; nam_apap224-1_60 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Academy Graduates, Kosch, Charles A. III, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; 1962; nam_apap224-1_61 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Academy Graduates, Liverpool, Henry, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_62 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Academy Graduates, Lodge, Robert, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1964; nam_apap224-1_63 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Academy Graduates, Mauter, David J., Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1958; 1960-1961; nam_apap224-1_64 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Academy Graduates, McKenney, John, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_65 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academy Graduates, Meler, Charles, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1959; nam_apap224-1_66 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Academy Graduates, Minicucci, Robert, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_67 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Academy Graduates, O'Keefe, Joseph, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1955-1956; nam_apap224-1_68 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Academy Graduates, Oster, George F., Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1959; 1961; nam_apap224-1_69 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Academy Graduates, Ross, Raymond H. Jr, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1959; nam_apap224-1_70 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Academy Graduates, Rumph, Robert, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1962; nam_apap224-1_71 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academy Graduates, Saacke, Paul, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1958-1959; nam_apap224-1_72 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Academy Graduates, Sanders, Thomas, Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1956-1961; nam_apap224-1_73 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Academy Graduates, Scott, Robert, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_74 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Academy Graduates, Smith, Robert Cortland, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1955-1961; nam_apap224-1_75 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Academy Graduates, Sullivan, Dennis, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1957; 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_76 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Academy Graduates, Ullman, Harlan, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1964; nam_apap224-1_77 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Academy Graduates, Von Freyman, Ronald, West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1958-1961; 1964; nam_apap224-1_78 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Academy Graduates, Westberg, Eric L., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1959-1960; 1962; nam_apap224-1_79 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Academy Graduates, Winter, Richard F., Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1955; nam_apap224-1_80 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Academy Graduates, Wood, Kenneth, Kings Point - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_81 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Academy Graduates, Young, Frank, Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1961; nam_apap224-1_82 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1953-1956; nam_apap224-1_83 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1957-1958; nam_apap224-1_84 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1960; nam_apap224-1_85 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1961; nam_apap224-1_86 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1962; nam_apap224-1_87 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1963; nam_apap224-1_88 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Academy, List of Candidates and Related Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1964; nam_apap224-1_89 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_90 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Agriculture, Dept.-Farmers Bulletins (Lists Of), 1963; nam_apap224-1_91 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Agriculture, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_92 (Box 2, Folder 32-33)
  - Agriculture, Legislation, Area Redevelopment Bill, 1963; nam_apap224-1_93 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Agriculture Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_94 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Air Force, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_95 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Appropriations, 1963; nam_apap224-1_96 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Appropriations, Foreign Aid, 1963; nam_apap224-1_97 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Appropriations, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_98 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Appropriations, Legislation, Foreign Aid, 1964; nam_apap224-1_99 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1958; nam_apap224-1_100 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-1_101 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1961; nam_apap224-1_102 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1962; nam_apap224-1_103 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1963; nam_apap224-1_104 (Box 3, Folder 14-18)
  - Armed Services Committee, Civil Defense, 1963; nam_apap224-1_105 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1958; nam_apap224-1_106 (Box 3, Folder 21-22)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1959; nam_apap224-1_107 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1960; nam_apap224-1_108 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1961; nam_apap224-1_109 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1962; nam_apap224-1_110 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Armed Services Committee, Correspondence, 1964; nam_apap224-1_111 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - Armed Services Committee, Defense Contracts, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-1_112 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Armed Services Committee, Hearings, 1962; nam_apap224-1_113 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Armed Services Committee, Investigating Defense Procurement, 1959-1960; nam_apap224-1_114 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Armed Services Committee, Military Pay Raise, 1963; nam_apap224-1_115 (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
  - Armed Services Committee, Military Pay Raise, 1963; nam_apap224-1_116 (Flat-file 2)
  - Armed Services Committee, Military Pay Raise, Worksheets, 1963; nam_apap224-1_117 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Armed Services Committee, National Military Airlift Subcommittee, 1960; nam_apap224-1_118 (Box 4, Folder 8-11)
  - Armed Services Committee, Reorganization of Defense Dept., 1958; nam_apap224-1_119 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Armed Services Committee, Reorganization of Defense Dept., 1958; nam_apap224-1_120 (Flat-file 1)
  - Armed Services Committee, Research and Development Subcommittee, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_121 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Armed Services Committee, Reserve Call Up Resolution, 1962; nam_apap224-1_122 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Armed Services Committee, Reserve Hearings, 1962; nam_apap224-1_123 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Armed Services Committee, Transportation Subcommittee, 1959; nam_apap224-1_124 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Armed Services Committee, Transportation Subcommittee, Seaboard Western Airlines, 1959; nam_apap224-1_125 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - Armed Services Committee, Trips, 1960; 1964; nam_apap224-1_126 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Armed Services Committee, Trips, 1961; nam_apap224-1_127 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
  - Armed Services Committee, Trips, Expense Accounts for Committee, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_128 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Armed Services Committee, Trips, Fort Dix, 1961; nam_apap224-1_129 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Armed Services Committee, Trips, 1962; nam_apap224-1_130 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Armed Services Committee, Utilization of Manpower Subcommittee, 1959; nam_apap224-1_131 (Box 4, Folder 26-28)
  - Armed Services Committee, Utilization of Manpower Subcommittee, 1960; nam_apap224-1_132 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Armed Services Committee, Utilization of Manpower Subcommittee, 1961; nam_apap224-1_133 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_134 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Army, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_135 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Army Engineer, Department, 1961; nam_apap224-1_136 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Army Engineer, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_137 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Army Reserve Investigation, 1962; nam_apap224-1_138 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Army Services, Reserve Forces and National Guard, 1962; nam_apap224-1_139 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, Department, 1963; nam_apap224-1_140 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Banking and Currency, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_141 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Banking and Currency, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_142 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Becker, Frank J., Bills, 1953-1954; nam_apap224-1_143 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Becker, Frank J., Photographs, 1959-1964; nam_apap224-1_144 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Becker, Frank J., Scholarship, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_145 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Becker, Frank J., Special Order, 1963; nam_apap224-1_146 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Becker, Frank J., Voting Record, 1961-1962; nam_apap224-1_147 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trade Meeting, 1962-1963; nam_apap224-1_148 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cases Closed, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_149 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_150 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights, Incoming Correspondence, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_151 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights, Petition Signatures Rockville Centre, 1963; nam_apap224-1_152 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights Commission, Department, 1964; nam_apap224-1_153 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Civil Service Committee, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_154 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Civil Service Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_155 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Committee, Legislation, 5% Increase Retirement, 1963; nam_apap224-1_156 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Coast Guard, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_157 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Commerce, Coast and Geodetic Survey, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_158 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commerce, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_159 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Customs, Department, 1957; 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_160 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Defense, Department, 1963-1964; nam_apap224-1_161 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - District of Columbia Committee, Crime D.C., Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_162 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - District of Columbia Committee, Legislation, 1963; nam_apap224-1_163 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - District of Columbia Committee, Legislation, 1964; nam_apap224-1_164 (Box 6, Folder 11)